sire-search.com 2017-06-17

# Privacy Policy - SIRE Life Sciences®

## Privacy Policy

The SIRE Life Sciences® online service is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe and secure user experience. We ensure that the information you submit via our website at [www.sire-search.com](http://www.sire-search.com/) remains private, and is only used for the purposes set out in this policy.

By registering and agreeing on our Terms and Conditions, you agree to receive offers, newsletters, promotions and updates from partners of SIRE Life Sciences®. You can withdraw your consent at any time by unsubscribing.

**How do we use the information we collect?**  
Your personal details, including your name, e-mail address and CV, are held and used by us for the following purposes: 

  * Matching your coded details with job vacancies, to assist us in finding you the position that most suits you.
  * Keeping you informed of SIRE Life Sciences® services, news and wider developments in your chosen field.
  * Compiling the salaries and other surveys of our candidates.

**Curriculum Vitae  **  
You can submit your CV at SIRE Life Sciences® by registering as a candidate. Although your CV will be stored online, it will only be accessible by SIRE Life Sciences® consultants that are working both inside and outside the European Union. Your CV will also be reviewed and stored in our databank. This databank, including the information relating to you, can be accessed by any of our consultants working in other offices of the SIRE Group, both inside and outside the European Union. You can update your CV at any time, simply by following the same procedure to submit a new CV. Your old CV will automatically be replaced.

**Access**  
You have the right at any time to ask us for a copy of the information supplied by you that we hold. We have the right to charge an administrative fee for this service. If you would like to make a request for information, please contact [admin@sire-search.com](mailto:admin@sire-search.com). You also have the right to ask SIRE Life Sciences® to stop using your information.

**Equal opportunities**  
SIRE Life Sciences® is an equal opportunities employer and a company committed to diversity. This means that all job applicants and members of staff will receive equal treatment and that we will not discriminate on grounds of gender, national origin, race, ethnic origin, skin color, nationality, sexual orientation, marital status, disability, religion or age.

**Disclosures of your information?**  
We will only share your information within the SIRE Group or companies where necessary to provide you with our recruitment services. It is possible that SIRE Life Sciences® could merge or be acquired by another business. If this happens, we may share the information that relates to you with the new owners of the business and their advisers. You will be sent notice of such an event. Your CV and related information will be sent to prospective employers. Such employers may be located both inside and outside the European Union. We may also release information relating to you to regulatory or law enforcement authorities, if required to do so. We also reserve the right to disclose the information we have collected about you to our consultants and to other persons from any aspect of the operation of its recruitment agency services. These third parties will be acting under similar undertakings of confidentiality as SIRE Life Sciences®.

**Use of  ** **cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that is sent from a web browser to a web browser when that browser visits the server's site. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. However, switching off cookies will restrict your use of our website.

**Functional cookies**  
Functional cookies are used on the www.sire-search.com website to remember your login, to track web traffic and to keep the session information such as your last search (this information is disposed every time you close your web browser).

**Analytics cookies**  
Analytics cookies are used to anonymously track user behavior on a website. SIRE Life Sciences® uses Google analytics to gain insight on how visitors are navigating on our website and how individual pages peform. We use this date to optimize our website and improve your overall experience of the visitors. If you require more information about analytics cookies, please check out the [Google Analytics Cookie usage on Websites](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) 

**Social media cookies**  
Visitors can't share content from SIRE Life Sciences® website to various social media platforms using ''share'' buttons. These share buttons only work if the social media platforms are allowed to place a third-party-cookie. This cookie is used by that social media platform to recognize if a visitor already has an account, making sharing content easier. These cookies are only placed after a visitor has clicked one of these sharing buttons.

**Advertising cookies**  
Also known as tracking cookies. These cookies store visitor behaviour and can identify visitors on one or multiple websites. This data allows advertising tools like Google AdWords and Google Doubleclick to show personalized ads, Making sure internet users get to see advertisements that they might be interested in.  

**Internet transferable information**  
Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy?**  
This privacy policy may be adjusted by SIRE Life Sciences® at any time. If we adjust or privacy policy in the future, we will set out those adjustments here. This way you will always know what personal information we gather, the purposes we might use it for and to whom we might disclose it to. If , at any time , you have questions or concerns about SIRE Life Sciences®' online commitment please feel free to contact us at admin@sire-search.com or call our local office to speak to one of our representatives.
